<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<root>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>31</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Brochure_March_2011.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology_March_2011.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>The report card for the Indian Mutual Fund industry for the quarter ended March 2011 is out. Marginal Equity Funds and Ultra Short Term Funds were the best performers in equity and debt categories, respectively, as per the latest ICRA Mutual Fund Ranking powered by ICRA Analytics Limited.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>In the Debt Funds category, Ultra Short Term Funds topped the chart followed by Debt Intermediate Funds and Liquid Funds. This category generated positive returns in the last quarter as compared to equity funds. It was mainly due to range bound bond market, the positive news in the Union budget lifted the market mood such as lower than expected fiscal deficit target for FY12 and higher investment ceiling for foreign funds to invest in the infrastructure bonds.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3></qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>32</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA Mutual Fund Ranking Brochure_June 2011.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>The report card for the Indian Mutual Fund industry for the quarter ended June 2011 is out. Mid &amp; Small Cap Funds and Ultra Short Term Funds were the best performers in equity and debt categories, respectively, as per the latest ICRA Mutual Fund Ranking powered by ICRA Analytics Limited.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>In the Debt Funds category, Ultra Short Term Funds topped the chart followed by Debt Intermediate Funds and Liquid Funds.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3>In the Equity Funds category, the average returns in the June quarter were mostly negative due to high crude oil prices, higher inflation number resulting into tight monetary policy by RBI and lower than expected GDP growth. Mid &amp; Small Cap Funds outperformed in the Equity category. The average return for Large Cap Funds in the June quarter was around -1.98%. In the same period benchmark indices, Nifty &amp; Sensex gave negative return of 3.07% and 2.96% respectively.</qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>33</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Brochure.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>The report card for the Indian Mutual Fund industry for the quarter ended September 2011 is out. Marginal Equity Funds and Debt Intermediate Funds were the best performers in equity and debt categories, respectively, as per the latest ICRA Mutual Fund Ranking powered by ICRA Analytics Limited.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>In the Debt Funds category, Debt Intermediate Funds topped the chart followed by Debt Long Term Funds and Ultra Short Term Funds. This category generated positive returns in the last quarter as compared to equity funds. It was mainly due to volatile bond market that provided much needed rally.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3>In the Equity Funds category, the average returns in the September quarter were mostly negative due to high inflation, tight monetary policy and global uncertainty. Marginal Equity Funds performed the best as their average equity exposure in equity is less than 65%. In the same period benchmark indices, Nifty &amp; Sensex gave negative return of 11.19% and 11.40% respectively.</qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>34</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>Annual_MF_Booklet_December_2011.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>The report card for the Indian Mutual Fund industry for the Year 2011 is out. Marginal Equity Funds and Ultra Short term Funds were the best performers in equity and debt categories, respectively, as per the latest ICRA Mutual Fund Ranking powered by ICRA Analytics Limited.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>In the Debt Funds category, Ultra Short Term Funds topped the chart followed by Debt Intermediate Funds and Liquid Funds. This category generated positive returns in the last calendar year as well. However in 2011 they have significantly outperformed equity funds. </qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3>In the Equity Funds category, the average returns for the Calendar Year 2011 were mostly negative due to high inflation, tight monetary policy and global uncertainty. Marginal Equity Funds performed the best as their average equity exposure in equity is less than 65%. In the same period benchmark indices, Nifty &amp; Sensex gave negative return of 24.61% and 24.64% respectively.</qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>35</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Brochure_March2012.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>The last quarter brought some relief to Indian equity markets, delivering positive return, thanks to the turnaround of investors’ sentiments in January and February. However, these gains were not sufficient to wipe out the losses made in the previous quarters, and over a 1-year period, returns delivered by average equity funds remained negative. The mid and small cap emerged as the best performing equity-oriented category, as the BSE Mid Cap index returned 23.5% over the past quarter, thereby erasing the accumulated losses incurred over the past one year.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>The average Ultra Short Term and Liquid Mutual Fund schemes were able to deliver 1-year returns equivalent to the present fixed deposit rates, while the institutional plans were able to deliver even better than the returns of fixed deposits.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3>For the 3-year period ending March 31, 2012, banking sector funds performed best, closely followed by mid and small-cap funds. The performance of the average Equity Tax Planning Funds and average Balanced Funds over the 3-year period were also impressive, while the actively managed Large-Cap Funds and Index funds were at the bottom of the chart within the equity funds category. Among the Fixed Income Funds, the debt intermediate category of funds performed best over the 3-year period, while long-term Gilt funds returned the lowest.</qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>36</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Brochure_June_2012.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>The equity markets remained volatile in the June quarter mainly due to poor macro-economic data which impacted investor sentiments. However, markets recovered in June over hopes of a rate cut and development in the Euro zone. This helped recover losses suffered in the previous two months of the quarter. The benchmark BSE Sensex closed the quarter at 17,430 compared to 17,404 in the beginning.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>Debt categories outperformed the equity in the one-year period ending June 2012. Debt Long Term and Gilt generated average returns of 9.50% mainly due to easing of yields. As there is an inverse relationship between bond yields and prices, softening of yields translate into higher prices and thus higher net asset value (NAV) for the fund. In comparison, large cap equity funds delivered -9.50% in the same period.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3>For three-year period ending June 2012, IT sector funds performed the best, closely followed by Banking sector funds. Among the debt funds, Ultra short-term and Liquid funds performed the best while long-term Gilt funds returned the lowest.</qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>37</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Brochure_Sept_2012.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>A total of 544 schemes were ranked across categories over the one-year period, while 464 schemes were ranked over the three-year period.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>During the quarter, the best performing category was the sector oriented banking equity funds, which delivered a return of over 14% during the September ending quarter. The next best performers were equity mid and small cap fund, with the average mid and small cap fund delivering an absolute return of 11.8% over the three-month period ending 28th September 2012. The performance of the mid and small category is in stark improvement over its performance in the previous quarter, where the average fund delivered a loss of 0.2%. At the prospect of an interest rate cut, longer term bond funds displayed a discernible improvement in performance between the last two quarters.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3>In the following pages, we present the star ranking assigned to the eligible funds for the quarter ending 30th September 2012.</qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
  <qtr>
    <qtrid>38</qtrid>
    <qtrBrocurePdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Brochure_Dec_2012.pdf</qtrBrocurePdf>
    <qtrRankingPdf>ICRA_Online_Mutual_Fund_Ranking_Methodology.pdf</qtrRankingPdf>
    <qtrdiv1>A total of 540 schemes were ranked across categories over the one-year period, while 465 schemes were ranked over the three-year period.</qtrdiv1>
    <qtrdiv2>For the year ending December 31, 2012, the BSE Sensex delivered 25.6%, while the BSE Mid-Cap and BSE Small-cap indices delivered 38.3% and 32.8%, respectively.  Compared to these indices, the best performing diversified equity fund managed to deliver 56%. The sector-oriented banking equity funds delivered the highest absolute returns, while the next best performers were equity mid and small-cap funds. At the same time, some of the best performing fixed income funds also managed to deliver double-digit returns.</qtrdiv2>
    <qtrdiv3> </qtrdiv3>
  </qtr>
</root>
